[{"answer": "Come on, my friend", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It was twenty minutes.  Like usual", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "They open a window", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Ten flights down", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You'd lose.  You'd die.  All over the sidewalk.  And into the street", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Get a stenographer", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend, what do you think this is", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No nothing", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Parochial school.  that place.  St. Android's", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I was expelled!  When I was fifteen", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "And all those like you", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Absolutely not.  I mean the wicked.  The heedless.  And their Las Vegas concubines", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "A fast.  To remind us of the poor, of those who must endure without enough to eat", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " No food.  Not until sundown", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Like this place", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Where's who", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I wouldn't even tell the Pope", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "And you listen to that", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hey, I know, it's hard.  But do what I do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, but... I don't know... sometimes", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " What you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey, I know, it's hard.  But do what I do", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Just tell him, I do love you, but I can't", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Three years.  Sister", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "A novice", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Bob", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So... hi there", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Look... I know I shouldn't have, I'm incredibly sorry about my friend, I wasn't thinking, I didn't know that would happen", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "But", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That man", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'd rather sing than do anything", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "It's better than springtime", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " That's true, wouldn't that be great.  Of course, we never know when things are going to change.  Any one of us could be transferred to another convent, tomorrow", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Oh no.  We'll always be together", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You're gonna be singing for that place if you don't get your ass out of here", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Calm down.  Think clearly.  my friend, do you have any idea who those men were", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "But... she was a showgirl.  She didn't have an old convent", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "But... she was a showgirl.  She didn't have an old convent", "docId": "Sister-Act.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "All right.  It's a beginning.  that place, that place", "qsentId": 42}]